Twelve chances to get it right.
12 Dates of Christmas is a romance, comedy,
fantasy film directed by James Hayman.
In an attempt to win back her ex-boyfriend Jack on Christmas Eve, Kate ends up
ruining her blind date with Miles, a handsome guy she's been set up with.
In a strange twist of fate, Kate is magically given the
chance to re-live Christmas Eve twelve times!
Kate Stanton, played by Amy Smart.
Miles Dufine, played by Mark-Paul Gosselaar.
Jack Evans, played by Benjamin Ayres.
Mike Stanton, played by Peter MacNeill.
Sally Stanton, played by Mary Long.
Margine Frumkin, played by Jayne Eastwood.
12 Dates of Christmas is a television film starring
Amy Smart and Mark-Paul Gosselaar.
It premiered on ABC Family on December 11, 2011 in their
25 Days of Christmas programming block.
It is directed by James Hayman.
The film depicts Smart as Kate, a woman insensitive to the feelings of others and who wants to return to a
past relationship, and Gosselaar as Miles, a widower who hopes to find a new romantic partner.
After Kate blows off her blind date with Miles on Christmas Eve, she discovers she is stuck in a time-loop,
giving her 12 chances to mature, improve her relationships with others, and find romance with Miles.
The film explores themes of new york city, christmas
party, blind date, time loop, falling in love.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and mind_bending.